Hello, I'm Kitami Jide.
I'm Kitami Jide. Nice to meet you. I'm the Inari Explorers.
Today, you'll be exploring the museum on your own.
I'd like to announce today's expedition.
Today's expedition is to think about the best way to dress up for your favorite activities.
It's been a long, long time, remember? It's been too long.
Today, we're going to ask Mr. Kitami to think about the best way to coordinate our activities.
I'm going to ask Kitami-san to come up with a guesswork coordination for us.
On the 3rd floor of Eavin's
Mr. Rigaud.
You said that, didn't you?
Why are you laughing?
I don't...
Am I wrong? Pronunciation.
No, I think it's fine.
It's, uh...
Can I have a word? Say it.
Yes, please.
How do you pronounce Mr. Rigaud? Gentlemen.
There's a lot of patterns.
Some people say Rigaud.
Rigaud.
Rigo.
Don't say it like Rigaud. Rigaud. Don't say it like Rigaud.
I didn't know how to pronounce it.
I just checked, and it's free style.
Freestyle.
What do you want to go with?
Rigo.
It's very grown-up.
I don't know if it's supposed to be adult. It's kind of low.
Rigaud's just opened on the 3rd floor.
I'd like to introduce you to the place.
Kitami-san is usually active as an idol.
I'm sure many of her fans have seen her wearing her "guesswork" outfit.
That's for sure.
Using that experience, today I'd like you to come up with your best guesswork coordination.
I see.
Let's move on to the store and get to work.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go!
Well then, we've arrived at the store.
Yay!
Here we are, ladies and gentlemen.
Nice to meet you. I'm sorry, I'm a little out of control.
Don't get in my car.
This way, right? We're here, but...
It's so big! It's so big!
It's one of the biggest in Tohoku.
You can't see it.
It's really big!
From here, we're going to start thinking about the "guessing game" coordinate.
Let's do it while looking at this corner where we are now.
Let's go!
I love it so much!
I'm tempted to say it.
Okay, let's take a look.
Let's see the front.
The front.
An example of how it's used.
It's already an idol.
It's for people who like anime.
Show the badge on the front like this.
Like this.
If you're a fan of Kitami-san, you can see her face.
That kind of thing.
Does it mean that the bar is on the front?
I don't see many of Mr. Kitami's fans using a board bag.
This is a good opportunity for all of you to try it.
It's true that there are many kinds of bags.
There are so many different kinds.
Please take a look.
Oh, but this one...
Is this for a woman?
I think this ribbon is removable.
I see.
And the colors...
There's also a more muted color.
I mean, I'm sure it's for your fan base.
I don't think the fans
I don't think it matters if it's for men or women.
as long as it's their favorite thing, they're happy to wear it.
It doesn't matter what it is.
Even if it's nice.
I don't need this.
What's this?
This is what I'm talking about.
Aigurumi for little stitches.
Little stitches?
If you get Kitami's dolls, you can put them in here.
Yes, it's cute!
I want this doll.
This doll?
That one?
Nothing's dyed yet.
That's for sure.
I just found it.
I can dye it my color.
What? What? Just a second. - What?
Say something exciting and I'll dye it my color.
Ta-da! Here you go.
Sewing clothes!
Aren't they selling a lot of them? Sewing clothes?
Stuffed clothes? Yes, they sell clothes.
Oh, my God! That's too cute!
What, you're gonna do a whole bunch of stuff with it?
Dressing them up. Really, yeah.
Like a dress-up doll.
I've heard of fans who sew costumes by hand and dress them up as stuffed animals.
Oh, there are?
Here, it's easy. The staff can buy them and change them.
Like a 10 cm friend?
It's the kind of store-bought stuff you'd expect to see.
This is a shocking image, but please don't spread it so wide.
Idols wear skirts that you can't see inside.
It's perfect. It's real.
She's so cute!
Very nice! Very cute!
So we can enjoy this too?
We can put them on our KOKESHI penlights.
You mean we can put them on our poppy's head? Yes, yes, yes.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
It's full of fun.
Where is this? Is this it?
Mauldaur. It fits the room.
Here, you see this? There's a lot of them over here.
You can make it yourself with this braid.
ae, it's all my own, so I can make it my own way.
Yes, you can make it with colorants.
And then you can put clothes on them.
I still have hats and stitches.
Wow, you're like Hikaru!
Like Hikaru.
We also have this.
And I'm doing it like this.
Making original dolls.
I didn't think this was possible in Tohoku.
I didn't think this was possible in Tohoku, but so far there are 4 stores in 4 places in the country.
It's really popular at Evin's.
I've always wanted to do it, but there's a line at the store.
I didn't think the old lady here could do it.
I'm sure the girls would be great at it.
It's definitely fun.
They say it's mainly because I'm already doing S-Corp.
Wait a minute. Isn't this amazing? This is...
I mean, it's like, "This is why it's so good." "This is why it's so good.
Especially since it's even in Hangul.
Kumi's favorite.
I love it. Korea's so popular.
That's why, with this Hangul...
I can make something like "Kitami-irin-ne" with this Hangul, you know.
Here's another one.
You can put your name on it.
It's so cool!
It's fun!
I wish this was private.
No, no, no.
I didn't want you guys to interrupt me again.
Interrupt me?
Interrupt me? I'm...
We're exploring together now.
Well, I'm glad we're doing this.
That feels good.
It's not too stuffy.
It's nice. There's a wide variety of colors.
It's rare to find all nine colors the same.
Here, we have them all. All the colors are here. Speaking of Tookoku...
There's this purple one, too, but this one is purple, so you can enjoy all kinds of purples.
That's for sure.
Applause! Nerd! I'm a Korean nerd too, so I'm a great nerd!
I'm definitely excited.
I was surprised to see that the board bags here come in very large sizes!
I can go on an expedition!
I can go on an expedition for sure!
Let's choose one of them for you!
I can't do patches today, but...
I've already cut it off
Love at first sight
I usually hold it like this
You're right
No one will know the sound
If you want to be exposed...
Are you sure you want to be exposed?
For example, that guy...
You and your favorite group.
Yes, yes, yes.
If you see someone wearing one of these...
Get one.
Swap them out.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
But even if I buy this...
I asked Tork to bring some of his goods today.
Let's do an example of how to put them in.
What's the best way to show them?
I can put it in here.
Boo-Boo, I'll get it for you.
Like this one, for example.
You can customize it to your own size.
You can customize it to fit your own size.
Oh, my God.
Wait a minute, it fits perfectly.
I don't know why I just made a composite.
Wait a minute.
You're advertising your own birthday.
He's advertising his birthday.
It's a bonus photo for the new collection.
Flowers.
They're so cute, they can make faces like this.
You can put tiny ones all over the place.
Or even a big one.
It's so good, so good, so good!
I'm going to fill it up
I'll fill it with my face.
My favorites.
Like raw photos.
It's so cute.
This one stands out a lot from a distance.
No, but it's not enough for me.
Not even close.
Even this?
Not enough.
Yes, yes, yes.
Ta-da!
Oh! What's this?
These are...
New penlights.
What color should box pushers have?
What color should I have?
Even though everyone likes the same color...
In such a case, right?
We have 1,2,3 now.
Well...
Six? Well, six for now.
You've brought a lot.
Well, first of all, we can customize these for you.
Like straps.
Yes, and the color of your choice.
If it's my guess, I'll have them all in purple.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you're a box person and you like everyone, you can do it like this.
Ha!
Yeah, and if it's your thumb, you can have another one.
I'm going to hold it like this, and I'm going to hold it like this
And if you hold the tools over here...
Ha!
It happened many times.
You're bringing a lot of stuff.
You see this guy? Who's this guy?
She looks like a gal.
It's too long.
If we support them with this...
I'm sure the box cows won't mind.
I knew it.
If you want them to try holding it...
Nine or ten cows...
There's nothing else to do but watch.
Yeah.
Are these penlights and straps
Are they sold separately?
Yes, they are.
It's very well done.
Yes, it is.
It's an autograph!
Almost.
Almost?
I was asked to write my name, so I wrote it, and then I realized it looked like this.
It's like I'm being tricked.
We have them.
I know...
We can use the cool ones, too.
I see.
But that's the campsite, right?
I want to carry around all these penlights.
Isn't this a lot of work to carry around?
That's why we give them to you.
I see.
Stored like this
It's spacious.
It's possible, but it's separated here.
There's a pocket here that lets you do that, so it's really convenient.
It's very convenient, so it won't break when it bumps into something.
It's so convenient that it won't break if it bumps into something, and it can be neatly stowed away.
Yes, it's getting more and more customizable.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to make it look cute.
I'm going to add to what I already have, and buy something new here to make it the best it can be.
Please put a dick in it, Kitami-san! No, it's a lie, a lie, a lie!
What? This is unofficial, right?
I've only ever seen you wearing it.
It's a very good look.
Shinjouko here!
And there's more!
There's a photo spot!
You can put your own custom noise group here and take a picture!
Maybe because it's in Sendai?
It's too much!
It's not just idols.
It's not just idols, but people who really like HIQ.
They asked me to make them wear something cute here.
and their uniforms...
I'd love for you to come and take pictures.
That's for sure.
I think it's going to turn on the lights. You know, like...
Oh, it's on!
This is amazing.
If this is my color
I don't know...
Wait a minute.
I'm getting a tummy ache.
It's just because it's a picture.
I'm sure there are times when you think of it that way
It's a little sad, but...
No, but I understand.
You can do it in your room.
You even made a spot like this.
It's amazing.
You can have so much fun in the store.
Look at this one.
It's just a cute bag.
So you can put all kinds of things in here?
Tiny size.
Tork's photos are large in size.
But if you are a customer of Tork, you can cut off the photos and put them in this bag.
You can put them in this bag, and you can do your business really quietly.
We also have bags like this.
Because, you know, on the back is this...
For those of us who don't want to be seen in public...
I think this kind of bag is delicious.
It sure looks like a stylish bag, doesn't it?
I'm the same way with all of mine.
I think it's very stylish.
If you think it's a stylish bag
I'm ready to work!
We support you, nerd!
Thank goodness we have you on our side.
That's great!
You're so full of life.
Too much.
Oh, man!
We've got a hell of a coordination!
It's done!
My favorite coords!
Water pearls
I got it!
You have a lot of character.
I like it.
You've got too much on, don't you?
Is this not a good idea? Are you sure you don't want to do this?
Of course we'll accept it. We'll accept anyone.
Is it okay? Is this...
Will the fans start a rumor that a nerd is here recently?
No, nerds tend to be show-offs.
I see.
I want them to see what I want first.
If someone came in here dressed like this, I'd look at them.
I would.
How did you feel today?
Well, it was good.
You're back here.
We met. It's such a great selection, mainstream co-op, cute and fun, and it's a nerd's best friend.
Really.
You can get everything here, so I definitely want everyone to get everything here.
You can come here to see the goods of your favorite activities, and you can also see the clothes.
We have camera clothes, as well as regular clothes.
We have everything you need, so please come!
Bibbins, 3rd floor.
Please come!
So that's it.
Today at 253
board bag
I've done the coordination.
You can customize it in your own way
Customize it as much as you like!
The possibilities are endless!
Make it your own!
Let's go!